

BEATRIZ **GARCÍA MARTÍN**

beatriz.garcia.martin24@gmail.com



+34 618.93.00.38



linkedin.com/in/beatrizgarcmar/



github.com/TrizBea24

ABOUT ME

Hello! I am Beatriz García, full stack developer. Recently I have finished the full stack development certification at the Bottega University. I invite you to check my projects in GitHub 🔗

My first approach to technology started when I built my first websites with WordPress. Then I designed and built an online shop with WooCommerce, which I have been managing for 5 years. Now I develop projects mainly with React, SASS, JavaScript, Python and Node.js. I'm always learning or improving my skills. Right now I'm improving my front-end with a course at General Assembly.

PROJECTS

HARRY POTTER CHARACTER FINDER 🔗



Web application with the main characters from Harry Potter. React, Python, SASS, JavaScript

PORTFOLIO WEBSITE 🔗



React, HTML, SASS, JavaScript

LANDING WEBSITE 🔗



HTML, SASS, Bootstrap

EDUCATION

Front-end Web Development course 2022 | General Assembly (ongoing)

Learning CSS, SASS, HTML, JavaScript, React, Typescript, Next.js, Git, Jest.

Certification in Full Stack Development 2022 | DevCamp by BOTTEGA | 600 h.

Certified in JavaScript, ReactJS, Python 3, UML, HTML5, CSS, Flask, JSON, Git, MongoDB, SQL Databases, SCSS/SASS, Flexbox, CSS Grid.

Master of International Cooperation for Development

2019 - 2022 | Universitat Jaume I

Master of Business Administration

2016 - 2018 | Universitat Oberta de Catalunya

Master in Corporate Communication

2012 - 2013 | Universidad Complutense de Madrid

Master's degree in Audiovisual Communication

2008 - 2012 | Universitat Politècnica de València Erasmus exchange 2011/12 in Dundalk (Ireland).

LANGUAGES

English C1 | Valencian C1 | French A2

EXPERIENCE

INTERNATIONAL COOPERATION OFFICER 2021 - 2022 | Fundación ONCE para América Latina

Project management and technical documentation.

ECOMMERCE MANAGER 🔗 2016 - 2021 | Mi tienda Nelybel

E-commerce design and technological development (WordPress, WooCommerce, HTML, CSS). Product management. Market research in order to detect new opportunities. Resolution of incidents. Customer service. Digital marketing strategy. (+10.000€ of sales in a single day).

COMMUNICATIONS OFFICER

2020 - 2021 | Dayvo Sistemas S.L.

Management of 20 accounts. Strategy and management of digital content and Ads on social networks.

DIVERSITY AND EMPLOYMENT ADVISOR

2019 - 2020 | Inserta Empleo/Fundación ONCE

Labour intermediation within the operational programme for social inclusion and social economy of the European Social Fund.

SALES AND SOCIAL SERVICES

2018 - 2019 | ONCE

Training on social services for people with visual impairment, leadership, team management, motivation and negotiation. Lottery sales (+20.000€ monthly turnover).

COMMUNICATIONS OFFICER

2014 - 2015 | Impulse.brussels (Brussels Enterprise Agency)

Responsible of the communication strategy and management in English of the cluster screen.brussels.

MARKETING AND COMMUNICATIONS ASSISTANT 2013 | Indra S.A.

Tracking Indra's reputation at media and refine and improve the corporate CRM. Collaboration in projects such as the launch of the new corporate Intranet and the definition of a working environment monitor.

SOFT SKILLS

- ★ Proactivity
- ★ Teamwork

- + Fast learning
- ★ Problem solving
- Commitment to diversity and sustainability



















